<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on abijango</title>
    <link>/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on abijango</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:21:20 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Adoption Rate</title>
      <link>/2018/09/06/android-adoption-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:21:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/06/android-adoption-rate/</guid>
      <description>So many years into Android and the adoption rate of the latest OS version is still a major shit show. OEM&#39;s doing their own thing and carriers opting for their own brand of &amp;ldquo;let&#39;s see how much we can fuck with the customers&amp;rdquo;.
 What a difference between the two platforms. The largest issue caused by this fragmentation is the inability to get critical updates out to the masses. Apple is about to release a brand new OS, and it will work on the vast majority of iPhones in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Netflix</title>
      <link>/2017/05/28/working-at-netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 10:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/28/working-at-netflix/</guid>
      <description>Just a small reminder to all of us that work environments do not need to be vile swamps filled with politics and nonsense. There are great places to work out there, we just haven&#39;t found them yet.
 The actual company values, as opposed to the nice-sounding values, are shown by who gets rewarded, promoted, or let go
 The excuses that this is the way the work environments are and there is no way to change them is just plain bullshit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MP3 is not dead, quit the panic</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/mp3-is-not-dead-quit-the-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/mp3-is-not-dead-quit-the-panic/</guid>
      <description>People can&#39;t really be blamed for losing their shit. All the click-bait articles were not helping. But seriously, everything is fine.
 But the “death” of the MP3 is really not much of a death at all. The files will not spontaneously combust. You&#39;ll still be able to buy and use MP3s. They will not suddenly stop playing.
  All this really does is move the classification of MP3 from being recognized as a file format of the moment to being a file format of the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple is 2 years behind</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/apple-is-2-years-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/apple-is-2-years-behind/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s be serious for a second, despite the absurdity of the statements like &amp;lsquo;is Apple the next Blackberry?&#39;. The only way Apple could be the next &amp;lsquo;Blackberry&amp;rsquo; is if they do what Blackberry did, i.e. refuse to change and evolve with the marketplace. We&#39;ve seen in the past that Apple does not do that. They delay product launches until they know they have a killer, or potentially amazing product. They watch the market like a hawk and work on a product to disrupt the market that actually makes a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>