<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Butterfly Dream on Butterfly Dream </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 10:29:21 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/2019/02/19/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 10:29:21 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/19/test/</guid>
      <description>blah blah</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars New Hope Animotion Trailer</title>
      <link>/2018/09/27/star-wars-new-hope-animotion-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 16:43:06 BST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/27/star-wars-new-hope-animotion-trailer/</guid>
      <description>This trailer looks so good. Somehow captures the feel of Star Wars.
Subtle nod to Han shot first ;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexa Meade Living Paintings</title>
      <link>/2018/09/20/alexa-meade-living-paintings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:42:25 BST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/20/alexa-meade-living-paintings/</guid>
      <description>This stuff is just stunning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Adoption Rate</title>
      <link>/2018/09/06/android-adoption-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:21:20 BST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/06/android-adoption-rate/</guid>
      <description>So many years into Android and the adoption rate of the latest OS version is still a major shit show. OEM&amp;rsquo;s doing their own thing and carriers opting for their own brand of &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s see how much we can fuck with the customers&amp;rdquo;.
 What a difference between the two platforms. The largest issue caused by this fragmentation is the inability to get critical updates out to the masses. Apple is about to release a brand new OS, and it will work on the vast majority of iPhones in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 16:28:35 BST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Naufal Mir. I am just a regular guy, living in London at the moment. I am highly opinionated and think too highly of myself. I write most of my opinionated pieces here on this blog, along with links to articles I find interesting plus a few original short story fiction pieces.
I am very into discussing ideas; especially controversial stuff, hence the nature of most of my posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Mania</title>
      <link>/2017/06/02/sonic-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 11:43:22 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/02/sonic-mania/</guid>
      <description>OMG OMG OMG!
2D Sonic once again! Yay! Childhood favourite game revival. These days nostalgia is all the rage, but still, this is Sonic!
 Sonic Mania, which is being developed by Headcannon and PagodaWest Games in collaboration with Sega and Christian Whitehead, will offer a mix of new levels and updated versions of classic Sonic stages. Sonic the hedgehog, Tails the fox and Knuckles the echidna will all appear in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Netflix</title>
      <link>/2017/05/28/working-at-netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 10:38:57 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/28/working-at-netflix/</guid>
      <description>Just a small reminder to all of us that work environments do not need to be vile swamps filled with politics and nonsense. There are great places to work out there, we just haven&amp;rsquo;t found them yet.
 The actual company values, as opposed to the nice-sounding values, are shown by who gets rewarded, promoted, or let go
 The excuses that this is the way the work environments are and there is no way to change them is just plain bullshit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MP3 is not dead, quit the panic</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/mp3-is-not-dead-quit-the-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:42:14 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/mp3-is-not-dead-quit-the-panic/</guid>
      <description>People can&amp;rsquo;t really be blamed for losing their shit. All the click-bait articles were not helping. But seriously, everything is fine.
 But the “death” of the MP3 is really not much of a death at all. The files will not spontaneously combust. You&amp;rsquo;ll still be able to buy and use MP3s. They will not suddenly stop playing.
All this really does is move the classification of MP3 from being recognized as a file format of the moment to being a file format of the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple is 2 years behind</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/apple-is-2-years-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:29:54 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/apple-is-2-years-behind/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s be serious for a second, despite the absurdity of the statements like &amp;lsquo;is Apple the next Blackberry?&amp;rsquo;. The only way Apple could be the next &amp;lsquo;Blackberry&amp;rsquo; is if they do what Blackberry did, i.e. refuse to change and evolve with the marketplace. We&amp;rsquo;ve seen in the past that Apple does not do that. They delay product launches until they know they have a killer, or potentially amazing product. They watch the market like a hawk and work on a product to disrupt the market that actually makes a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel&#39;s Gifted</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/marvels-gifted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:23:14 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/marvels-gifted/</guid>
      <description>If this is anywhere near as good as Heroes (Yes I am a huge fan of Heroes), this could be good!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates pirating Pirates</title>
      <link>/2017/05/16/pirates-pirating-pirates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 14:20:38 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/16/pirates-pirating-pirates/</guid>
      <description>This made me laugh this morning.
 Hackers claim to have stolen the upcoming Pirates of the Caribbean film and are demanding that Disney pay a ransom or else have it released online.
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oldest Star Wars Fan</title>
      <link>/2015/11/27/the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:29:56 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/11/27/the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</guid>
      <description>The first guy who ever realised what a success Star Wars was going to be. Just before the new movie comes out, and people still bashing Star Wars. Eat your hearts out haters!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hijab - Taking Over the Whole Conversation</title>
      <link>/2015/05/28/hijab-taking-over-the-whole-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 11:29:56 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/28/hijab-taking-over-the-whole-conversation/</guid>
      <description>I read an article on medium, I&amp;rsquo;m tired of hijab from a lady who seems to be sick of the hijab taking over her life. Or rather, all the important conversations in her life leaving her own personal identity out in the cold.
She has written other articles on the matter, all of them carrying the same tone. Frustration, annoyance, even outright rage. I can not say that I can being to understand the sentiment, only rather I would like to talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside ILM</title>
      <link>/2015/05/27/inside-ilm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 14:01:13 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/27/inside-ilm/</guid>
      <description>A must read. From Origin Story to industry dominance. You may not like Star Wars or George Lucas, but you do owe them the amazing visual effects that you have in movies.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Netflix Is Fixing the TV</title>
      <link>/2015/05/27/how-netflix-is-fixing-the-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 13:32:09 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/27/how-netflix-is-fixing-the-tv/</guid>
      <description>Getting better TVs is always going to be a good thing for us the consumers. Look at smartphones, if they were taking 5-10 seconds to turn on like TVs do these days, how much would we use them?
And I love the fact that Samsung still doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a Netflix certified TV :).
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

