<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Abijango</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Abijango</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 16:43:32 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abijango.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla Model 3 Performance, 6 month ownership review</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2020/03/10/tesla-model-3-performance-6-month-ownership-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 16:43:32 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2020/03/10/tesla-model-3-performance-6-month-ownership-review/</guid><description>This started of as an initial first impressions piece, and as I did not publish it over the weeks leading to months, it turned into a full blown review, though a very casual one, no feeds and speeds comparisons found here. If you are interested in that, I am sure there are many, many posts online comparing this car to every possible car out there.
This is just my experience and impressions of how and where my obsession with Tesla started, a short history down memory lane, and how I found the process of buying and owning this in a daily capacity.</description></item><item><title>How Iceland reduced teenage substance abuse</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2020/03/03/how-iceland-reduced-teenage-substance-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 09:56:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2020/03/03/how-iceland-reduced-teenage-substance-abuse/</guid><description>It all started with psychologist asking the right questions:
“Any college kid could say: why do they start? Well, there’s availability, they’re risk-takers, alienation, maybe some depression,” he says. “But why do they continue? So I got to the question about the threshold for abuse and the lights went on – that’s when I had my version of the ‘aha’ experience: they could be on the threshold for abuse before they even took the drug, because it was their style of coping that they were abusing.</description></item><item><title>Worship at the altar of Acros</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2020/02/06/worship-at-the-altar-of-acros/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 15:34:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2020/02/06/worship-at-the-altar-of-acros/</guid><description>The Fujifilm Neopan Acros or simple Acros as it is referred to, is sadly one of the discontinued film stocks that Fujifilm produced for many years. Though there is some rumours that it might come back, 🤞🏽.
The Fujifilm X-series cameras from the X-Pro2 onwards, X-T2, X100F and all the newer ones have the Acros film simulation built into the cameras. This is one of the reasons I stuck to Fuji cameras when at first I had picked up the X-T2 somewhat by accident.</description></item><item><title>Nintendo Switch overtakes SNES with more than 52 million sold</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2020/01/31/nintendo-switch-overtakes-snes-with-more-than-52-million-sold/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 09:54:17 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2020/01/31/nintendo-switch-overtakes-snes-with-more-than-52-million-sold/</guid><description>John Gruber writing over at Daring Fireball, linking to an article for the Verge:
The Switch is a hit because the games are great, but the OS is also a triumph, and contributes to the joyfulness of using it.
I’ve only played a few Switch games when a friend generously lent me his Switch to try out Breath of the Wild (An amazing game), but besides the games, the Switch is a delight to use.</description></item><item><title>Self Driving DeLorean is taught to Drift</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2020/01/02/self-driving-delorean-is-taught-to-drift/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:51:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2020/01/02/self-driving-delorean-is-taught-to-drift/</guid><description>This is just insane! I want this on my Tesla like yesterday! Please please please Elon make it happen 😂
Completing the “MARTYkhana” course on the first attempt was awesome, but he knew that the one-of-a-kind data gleaned from the run could transform the capabilities of autonomous driving systems found in cars today.
First try? 😂 Not really but woah!</description></item><item><title>The voice at embankment station</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/12/13/the-voice-at-embankment-station/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:15:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/12/13/the-voice-at-embankment-station/</guid><description>When people come together for a simple human kindness :).</description></item><item><title>One man tries Windows after 20 years</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/11/05/one-man-tries-windows-after-20-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 13:47:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/11/05/one-man-tries-windows-after-20-years/</guid><description>It went almost exactly how you would expect :)
I especially liked this tidbit:
Want to run Docker for Windows on your brand new Surface Laptop 3? Sorry, can’t do that without buying an upgrade to Windows Pro (the $1800 Surface Laptop 3 apparently wasn’t expensive enough to warrant that designation, so it ships with the Home edition. Okay, sheesh).
😂😂😂</description></item><item><title>Street photography with the X100F (Day 0)</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/10/01/street-photography-with-the-x100f-day-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 15:18:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/10/01/street-photography-with-the-x100f-day-0/</guid><description>Ever since getting the X100F I have been using it on and off. I have a more detailed post coming at some point with my thoughts on the camera itself. Spoiler alert: It is freaking amazing!
But till then, enjoy some of the first few street pictures I have taken with the camera.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson is shadier than you thought</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/10/01/boris-johnson-is-shadier-than-you-thought/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:16:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/10/01/boris-johnson-is-shadier-than-you-thought/</guid><description>Not only has Boris used his infamous ‘dead cat strategy’ to move the conversation away from him and Carrie Symonds and his plans for Brexit, he’s managed to push down his past mistakes on Google, too — making it more difficult for people to get a quick snapshot of relevant information. He’s not just controlling the narrative here — he’s practically rewriting it. And judged by the standards of an SEO campaign, it’s hard to describe it as anything other than a resounding success.</description></item><item><title>The Tesla advantage</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/24/the-tesla-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 15:16:17 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/24/the-tesla-advantage/</guid><description>From industry expert analysis:
Even modern EVs from veteran carmakers are finding it hard to match the Roadster’s 245-mile EPA range. The Audi e-tron, for example, just has 204 miles of range per charge, while the award-winning I-PACE has an EPA rating of 234 miles per charge.
Tesla’s advantage or so, can be narrowed down to a few things:
All-electric only design, instead of converting existing platforms for EVs.</description></item><item><title>A day in London with family</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/24/a-day-in-london-with-family/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 11:53:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/24/a-day-in-london-with-family/</guid><description>A few images from the day roaming the streets of London. Didn’t get a lot of keepers, but oh well, that’s how it goes sometimes. 🤷🏽‍♂️</description></item><item><title>Supercharger at Nürburgring</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/23/supercharger-at-n%C3%BCrburgring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 15:23:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/23/supercharger-at-n%C3%BCrburgring/</guid><description>We installed a Supercharger at Nürburgring. Makes it feel like home, you know? pic.twitter.com/x1tPjI7bi0
&amp;mdash; Tesla (@Tesla) September 18, 2019 So long suckaaaa’s at Porsche 😃
Data from our track tests indicates that Model S Plaid can achieve 7:20 at the Nürburgring. With some improvements, 7:05 may be possible when Model S returns next month.
&amp;mdash; Tesla (@Tesla) September 19, 2019</description></item><item><title>X-Pro3 the Design Failure before a single test 😂</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/23/x-pro3-the-design-failure-before-a-single-test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 15:02:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/23/x-pro3-the-design-failure-before-a-single-test/</guid><description>Olaf Sztaba writing on his blog about the uproar on the internet on the new design that Fujifilm revealed for the highly anticipated X-Pro3.
First, nobody or almost nobody who is crying wolf has had a chance to shoot with this camera yet. Luckily, it appears that a physical camera is no longer needed to prove its usefulness to the world. People just know! What a brilliant bunch! Saves a lot of hassle.</description></item><item><title>Twitter Gold as usual</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/twitter-gold-as-usual/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 16:02:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/twitter-gold-as-usual/</guid><description>Oh how much would I like to work at SpaceX or Tesla! 😭
Droid Junkyard, Tatooine pic.twitter.com/yACFR9y04P
&amp;mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) September 17, 2019</description></item><item><title>Daredevil Might Return</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/daredevil-might-return/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/daredevil-might-return/</guid><description>I want Daredevil back! Out of all the Marvel TV series, I think Daredevil was clearly the best, with Punisher a close second. I think they lost the plot with Iron Fist and Luke Cage (really? What was that). Jessica Jones was just OK.
There is so much more that can be done with the medium and the stories coming straight of the comics, modified for modern TV audiences, see HBO Watchmen.</description></item><item><title>Deepest place on earth</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/deepest-place-on-earth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/17/deepest-place-on-earth/</guid><description>I love the Kurzgesagt videos! This one was particularly interesting.</description></item><item><title>Cyberpunk 2077 Twitter is a mega troll</title><link>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/12/cyberpunk-2077-twitter-is-a-mega-troll/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://abijango.github.io/2019/09/12/cyberpunk-2077-twitter-is-a-mega-troll/</guid><description>Whoever this person is, I give him 9000 troll points!
We have a feeling that this design is going to stick around. #2077 pic.twitter.com/Box6pG6Tee
&amp;mdash; Cyberpunk 2077 (@CyberpunkGame) September 10, 2019</description></item></channel></rss>